easiestsalessystem.com 2014-12-23

# Welcome!

**_Updated 7_/2014_**

**PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING OR ACCESSING ANY PART OF THE** **EASIEST SYSTEM EVER** **WEBSITE OR ITS SERVICES.**

**I. OVERVIEW**

Easiest System Ever, L.L.C. ("ESE," "we," or "us") respects the privacy of users of ESE's websites, including www.easiestsalessystem.com and http://newwebcopycat.com (the "Websites") and other related ESE services (collectively, the "Services"). The following privacy policy (the "Policy") tells you about the information that ESE collects through the Services and how ESE may use or disclose such collected information. 

By accessing the Services, continuing to access the Services, or submitting any information through the Services, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy, as modified from time to time by us, as described below. Your use of the Services is also governed by the Terms of Service, which are expressly incorporated into this Policy. 

**II. UPDATES**

ESE reserves the right to make changes to this Policy at any time, and will post any revised Policy on this page. You will know we have changed the Policy when you see a new updated date at the top of this Policy. ESE will not notify the Services' users of any such changes by e-mail or other personal contact. We encourage you to check the date of this Policy whenever you visit the Services so that you will know when you need to review the Policy for modifications. 

**III. INFORMATION COLLECTION**

ESE may collect and store any information you voluntarily submit or upload through the Website or Services, whether through your request for more information, registration, purchase, or otherwise. Such information may include name, email address, billing and payment information, contact information, personal preferences, or any other information submitted by any user through the Services. 

ESE collects information about how you found ESE, including determining the identity of an individual that referred you to ESE through a hyperlink associated with that individual. 

ESE may collect passive information about your visit or use of the Services, including the date and time of your visit, the length of your visit, the specific Website pages, profiles, or feeds you visited, your IP address, the type of web browser and operating system used, and the address of any website that directed you to the Services. ESE may also collect and aggregate usage information related to your use of the Services. 

In addition, we may use cookies, web beacons, local shared objects (sometimes called "flash cookies"), or other similar technology in connection with your use of the Services (collectively, "Cookies"). Cookies are small data files that may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Services, such as your browser type, search preferences, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. You can disable some (but not all) Cookies in your device or browser settings, but doing so may affect your ability to use the services provided through the Services. 

ESE does not necessarily take action in response to do-not-track signals or similar mechanisms. Additionally, third-party service providers may collect tracking information even if you have enabled your browser’s do-not-track functionality or utilized a similar do-not-track mechanism. 

**IV. INFORMATION USE PRACTICES**

ESE may use the personal information or other information or data collected, individually or in the aggregate, as described above, for any lawful purpose, including such purposes as determining the affiliate or other individual that referred you to ESE, determining your membership in certain MLM companies; determining your eligibility for participation in ESE programs, analyzing and tracking the level or type of user activity on the Website and Services, tracking and analyzing usage trends, personalizing the Services to better reflect your preferences, or enhancing your and other users' use of the Services. ESE may also use your submitted information to contact you, via e-mail, telephone, or otherwise, regarding your request for more information, enrollment with third-party companies, enrollment with ESE, the sale of products offered by ESE or its partners, or regarding your use of the Services or your account. 

**V. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

In the event you were referred to ESE, directly or indirectly, by an individual or affiliate, ESE will disclose your information to that individual or affiliate. Specifically, ESE will disclose your submitted information, including name, email address, telephone number, and any other information you voluntarily submit through the Service, to the individual associated with the hyperlink that you clicked to access the ESE registration process. ESE is not responsible for the affiliate's use or disclosure of your personal information. ****

ESE may use third-party companies, agents, or contractors to perform services on our behalf. For example, ESE may partner with other companies to personalize our web pages, process credit card transactions, collect debts, analyze or enhance the data collected by the Services (including user's interaction with the Services), or otherwise assist ESE in better serving the Services' users. During the course of providing ESE with these services, these third-parties may have access to your personal and non-personal information. These companies are not permitted to use your personal information except for the purpose of providing the services we request of them. 

ESE may partner with third-party companies, agents, or contractors in order to offer users joint promotions, advertisements, programs and marketing campaigns in which we believe our users may be interested. These companies are not permitted to use your personal information except for the purpose of participating in the promotional arrangement for which ESE engages them. 

ESE may disclose your personal and non-personal information or other collected data, individually or in the aggregate, as described above, to third-party companies in order to allow such third-parties to better serve their existing customers and to solicit prospective customers. Such third-parties may use the disclosed personal information to make promotional or other offers directly to you, to better understand the company's potential customers and their preferences, or to otherwise personalize or enhance their marketing campaigns. Such third-parties may use the disclosed personal information to contact you by means of email advertising, text/short message services, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, or other means of advertising. By voluntarily using the Services you consent to the disclosure of your collected information for these purposes. 

ESE also reserves the right to disclose personal information when we reasonably believe disclosure is required by law, if we reasonably believe disclosure is necessary to establish or exercise legal rights, or in situations involving potential threats to physical safety. 

In the event that ESE is acquired by or merged with a third party, we reserve the right, to sell or otherwise transfer any and all information we have collected from you as part of that transaction and such third party will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Policy. 

**VI. THIRD-PARTY LINKS**

The Services may contain links to websites not owned or controlled by ESE. ESE does not necessarily review or endorse the content of these linked websites. You should review the terms of service and privacy policies of all websites you visit. 

**VII. SECURITY**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information we collect on the Services. Unfortunately, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% effective. Accordingly, we cannot absolutely guarantee the security of your personal information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it. You are responsible for restricting access to your computer or mobile device through which you access the Services. Users of public or shared computers or unprotected mobile devices should log out at the completion of each visit to our Services. By using the Services, or providing personal information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of these Services. 

**VIII. DATA RETENTION**

ESE may retain the personal and non-personal information or other collected data, individually or in the aggregate, as described above, after you delete your account. However, ESE does not guarantee that any information will continue to be available after such deletion. 

**IX. VIEWING AND UPDATING INFORMATION**

You are responsible for updating and maintaining the accuracy of your personal information that you provide to or through the Services. If you would like to update your contact information, you may do so by visiting your account page on the Website or contacting ESE at the address below. If you believe you have submitted inaccurate information through the Services, and would like ESE to change such information, please contact ESE customer support at _easiestsystemever@gmail.com_

**X. CONTACT**

If you have questions concerning this privacy policy, please email _easiestsystemever@gmail.com_

Our address is: 

Easiest System Ever LLC 

10945 State Bridge Rd Suite 401-274 

Alpharetta, GA 30022 

Telephone: 770-573-4694 

1181389.02
